const quizData = [
    {
        question: "Which dinosaur had the largest brain for its body size?",
        options: ["Stegosaurus", "Triceratops", "Troodon", "Tyrannosaurus Rex"],
        answer: "Troodon"
    },
    {
        question: "What period did the Tyrannosaurus Rex live in?",
        options: ["Jurassic", "Cretaceous", "Triassic", "Permian"],
        answer: "Cretaceous"
    },
    {
        question: "Which dinosaur was known as the 'king of the dinosaurs'?",
        options: ["Velociraptor", "Tyrannosaurus Rex", "Brachiosaurus", "Allosaurus"],
        answer: "Tyrannosaurus Rex"
    },
    {
        question: "Which dinosaur had a long neck and tail and was one of the largest animals to ever walk the earth?",
        options: ["Stegosaurus", "Triceratops", "Brachiosaurus", "Velociraptor"],
        answer: "Brachiosaurus"
    },
    {
        question: "Which dinosaur had a distinctive crest on its head?",
        options: ["Parasaurolophus", "Triceratops", "Spinosaurus", "Ankylosaurus"],
        answer: "Parasaurolophus"
    },
    {
        question: "Which dinosaur was known for having a large sail-like structure on its back?",
        options: ["Spinosaurus", "Allosaurus", "Diplodocus", "Iguanodon"],
        answer: "Spinosaurus"
    },
    {
        question: "Which dinosaur is believed to have had the strongest bite force?",
        options: ["Allosaurus", "Tyrannosaurus Rex", "Velociraptor", "Giganotosaurus"],
        answer: "Tyrannosaurus Rex"
    },
    {
        question: "Which dinosaur is known for the three horns on its face?",
        options: ["Triceratops", "Stegosaurus", "Baryonyx", "Ankylosaurus"],
        answer: "Triceratops"
    },
    {
        question: "Which dinosaur was the largest known carnivore?",
        options: ["Giganotosaurus", "Spinosaurus", "Tyrannosaurus Rex", "Carnotaurus"],
        answer: "Spinosaurus"
    },
    {
        question: "Which small dinosaur was known for its speed and agility?",
        options: ["Velociraptor", "Stegosaurus", "Diplodocus", "Allosaurus"],
        answer: "Velociraptor"
    }
];
